# Tania o'harlem

#### **UX DESIGNER**

New York, NY - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Tania-o'harlem/a66fea1d90c033df

Creative, enthusiastic, professional with 14+ years experience in front-end UI development and graphic design. Co-founder of a successful design and consultancy business, specializing in brand identity, personal style and various projects for print, web and advertising.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **UX DESIGNER**

Billboard - New York, NY - May 2015 to October 2015

New York (USA), contract

Design, UI, navigation, JS and graph data visualization for the Billboard Medusa project.

#### **DEVELOPER**

UX DESINGER - New York, NY - November 2014 to September 2015

Famebeat, New York (USA), contract

Brand identity development, template design, UX development.

#### **UX CONSULTANT/DEVELOPER**

More & More Group Inc - New York, NY - January 2013 to November 2014

New York (USA)

Magento Enterprise theme/template design and development.

#### **UX/FASHION CONSULTANT**

The Hollywood Reporter - Los Angeles, CA - 2014 to 2014

The Hollywood Reporter, Los Angeles (USA), contract

Pret-a-Reporter UX, content strategy, template design, fashion looks.

## ART DIRECTOR, CO - FOUNDER

CREATIVE - Mockba - October 2001 to December 2012

RedStyle design studio, Moscow (Russia) and New York (USA)

Art direction and supervision of a creative team of designers, copywriters and front-end developers. Idea generation, concept development, visualization, design supervision.

Project types: digital/web, UX, brand identity, corporate style, graphics & illustration, print, film, interactive, fashion, interior design, corp. Intranet systems.

Clients: Mitsubishi Motors (automotive), Krusovice (food & beverages), Aleś Michalevič (politics), Drive Dance Project (entertainment), Sunlight (jewelry), EPL Diamond (jewelry), Nadine Interiors (architect & design studio), Tourtrans Voyage (tourism), The Third Level (movie), Magnet (supermarket store chain). More info at www.redstyle.ru

**EDUCATION** 

### **BFA in GRAPHIC DESIGN**

Moscow Architectural Institute - Москва 1993 to 1997

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Flash), QuarkXPress, Sketch.
- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS, LESS, responsive, mobile-first, cross-browser compatibility
- JavaScript/jQuery, Ajax, JSON, extJS, CytoScape.js, , git, PHP, Magento, Drupal 6/7, Symfony/ Twig, Underscore, Swiper, Wordpress templates.
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), MAC environment.
- Strong aesthetic sense, understanding of print design & typography, knowledge of web standards and fashion trends